

231 Cocksfield Avenue, North York, ON, M3H 3T6 Canada

□ (+1) 226-505-8235 | 🗷 mayurhadole@gmail.com | 🎋 www.mayurhadole.com | 🖸 MayurHadole | 🛅 mayur-hadole

Summary _

Software Engineer with experience in event-driven systems. Proficiency in operating multi-region distributed streaming platforms like Apache Kafka on AWS and On-premise. Proficient in provisioning and operating Data ETL systems using technologies like Airflow, DBT, Kafka, Snowflake on public cloud like AWS. Ample software development life-cycle experience exercised from start to finish along with prominent communication skills and constructive attitude.

Skills

Programming Java, Python, C/C++, Linux, MYSQL, VHDL, Verilog

Big Data Confluent Kafka, Kafka Connect, Snowflake, DBT, Avro, JSON.

AWS S3, AWS Secrets Manager, AWS Managed Airflow(MWAA), AWS Lambda, AWS IAM, AWS SageMaker, AWS CloudWatch, AWS Cloud

SES, AWS SNS, AWS CloudFormation.

Terraform, SaltStack, GitHub Actions, Docker, GitLab, GitHub, BitBucket, Ansible, Bamboo, Jenkins, Maven, SonarQube, JIRA, **DevOps Tools**

Confluence, Asana

HTML5, CSS, JavaScript, TypeScript, React, Angular, Bootstrap Framework, Web

English, Hindi, Marathi, Gujarati. Languages

Work Experience _____

Tucows Toronto, Ontario, Canada

DATA INTEGRATION DEVELOPER July. 2021 - Present

· Design, build, secure, implement and maintain Data ETL platform with DBT, Airflow, Kafka and Snowflake

- · Build automation to provision, maintain, and monitor all aspects of Kafka, Airflow and AWS SageMaker environment via infrastructure as code.
- · Successful migration of on-premise data ETL job orchestration system (Airflow) to AWS managed Airflow
- · Administered Data Lake (Snowflake) using Terraform
- Deployed AWS Python Lambdas to create and deliver usage reports
- Implemented CI/CD for Machine learning Pipelines using Terraform and AWS SageMaker
- Used Terraform, SaltStack, GitHub Actions etc. to implement CI/CD pipelines for Kafka and Airflow
- · Conceived and wrote detailed software implementations while ensuring that their code adhere to the security, logging, error handling, and performance standards and non-functional requirements.
- Skills: Application Development (Python, Java, KafkaStreams, KafkaConnect, JUnit), AWS (IAM, S3, Lambda, Managed Airflow, SageMaker, SQS, SNS, CloudWatch, CloudFormation) Other(Terraform, Docker, SaltStack, Airflow, DBT, Snowflake, GitHub Actions, Jira, Confluence, Asana).

BMO Financial Group Toronto, Ontario, Canada

DEVELOPER

Jan. 2020 - July 2021

- Design, build, secure, implement and maintain Multi-data-center Kafka infrastructure.
- Build automation to provision, maintain, and monitor all aspects of the Kafka environment via infrastructure as code.
- To meet stringent Recovery Point Objective (RPO), converted traditional Kafka clusters to multi region clusters.
- · Helped build real-time streaming data pipelines to reliably get data between systems and applications.
- Identify bottlenecks and tune to optimize Kafka performance and throughput.
- Built real-time streaming applications Kafka streams that transform & react to streams of data.
- · Conceived and wrote detailed software implementations while ensuring that their code adhere to the security, logging, error handling, and performance standards and non-functional requirements.
- · Automating on-boarding of clients to Kafka by developing CI/CD pipelines for Kafka Streams, Topics, ACLs, Schemas, Kafka Connectors etc.
- Skills: Application Development (Java, KafkaStreams, KafkaConnect, JUnit), Other (JSON, AVRO, WSDL, HTML, CSS3, JavaScript, Angular, Git, Ansible, Bamboo, Jira, Confluence).

Orbis Communications Hamilton, Ontario, Canada

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER (CONTRACT)

- Oct. 2019 Dec. 2019 • Enhancement & bug fixes in Java based backend.
- Frontend changes using JavaScript, jQuery and CSS
- Skills: Application Development (Java, Spring, JSP, Hibernate, SQL, JUnit, ¡Query, JavaScript, HTML/CSS), Scripting (Bash, Python), Other(BitBucket, Jira, HTML/CSS).

MAYUR HADOLE · RÉSUMÉ NOVEMBER 16, 2021

TD Bank
Toronto, Ontario, Canada

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER Mar. 2018 - Jun. 2019

- Design & Develop Spring Batch jobs in Java using dependency management and build tool Maven.
- REST API development using JAVA 8, Spring Boot, Spring, JPA/Hibernate and unit tests.
- Develop SQL stored procedures to perform data intensive logic and Shell Scripts for file manipulation, Job dependencies etc.
- Cross-communicated between development teams to design blueprints of common Java classes and ensure they would perform correctly upon completion
- Excellent time-management and multi-tasking skills through simultaneous tight deadline driven projects and tasks.
- Skills: Application Development (Java, Spring Batch, JDBC, Hibernate, JUnit), Scripting (Bash, Python), Other (Jenkins, Bitbucket, Sonar Qube, Confluence, Jira, HTML/CSS).

Education

Conestoga College Kitchener, Ontario, Canada

POST GRAD DIPLOMA IN EMBEDDED SYSTEMS DEVELOPMENT

2016 - 2017

- Relevant Courses: Operating Systems, Data Structures and Algorithms, Embedded Programming (C/C++)
- Award: Dean's Honors List Recognition and first rank for Capstone project (IoT Horticulture Systems)

Government Engineering College

Gandhinagar, Gujarat, India

2012 - 2015

BACHELOR IN ELECTRONICS & COMMUNICATION ENGINEERING
• Relevant Courses: C/C++ Programming, Verilog, VSDL, Communication Skills

N.G. Patel Polytechnic

Bardoli, Gujarat, India

DIPLOMA IN ELECTRONICS & COMMUNICATION ENGINEERING

• Award: Silver Medal (Recognition for Academic Achievement)

2009 - 2012